Guide to the Archives of Irish America County Societies Collection AIA.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- XXV. Roscommon, 1931-2001
  - Financial Correspondence, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Financial Correspondence: St. Patrick's Night Annual Ball, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Financial: Dinner-Dance Accounts, 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Football Club Fall Dinner-Dance, 1994-1995, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Histories, 1961-1976 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Installation of Officers, 1968, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Membership Dues, 1960-1967 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Membership Dues, 1698-1977 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Membership Dues, 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Membership: Monthly Letters, 1973, 1983-1987 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, Jul 16, 1931-Dec 31, 1945; cuid821 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, Jan 1, 1946-Dec 31, 1952; cuid822 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, Jan 1, 1953-Dec 31, 1954; cuid823 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Minutes, 1955; cuid824 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Minutes, 1956; cuid825 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Minutes, 1957; cuid826 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Minutes, 1958; cuid827 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, 1959; cuid828 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1960; cuid829 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1961; cuid830 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1962, 1984; cuid831 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1986, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Reunion Dinner-Dance, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - St. Patrick's Ball, 1964-1976 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - St. Patrick's Ball, 1977-1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - St. Patrick's Ball, 1981-1986 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - St. Patrick's Celebration, 1954 (Box Shared Tamiment 003, Folder 12)
  - St. Patrick's Celebration and Reunion Dinner-Dance, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - St. Patrick's Dinner-Dance, 1983, 2004, undated (Box 15, Folder 12, Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Stationery, circa 1980-1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Yearbook, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Yearbook, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Dinner-Dance, circa 1950-19709 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Dinner-Dance, circa 1970-1989 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: Reunion Dinner-Dance, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: Social and Welfare Leagues, Inc. St. Patrick's Ball, Hotel Ritz Carleton (Panorama,framed), Mar 16, 1946 (Box Shared Tamiment AIAXOS001, Folder 1)
- XXVI. Sligo, 1963-2007
  - Football Club of New York Annual Dinner Dance, 1990, 1996, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Ladies Social and Benevolent Assocation Golden Jubilee Dinner Dance, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association 85th Anniversary Program, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Anniversary Dance, 1991-1993 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1988-1990 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Book of Arrangements and Committees, 1906-1927 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Minutes, 1932-1954 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 1994, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 2000-2001, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association: Ledger, 1900-1929 (Box 68)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Due to the fragility of this item, cradles must be used.
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association: Ledger, 1966-1984 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Treasurer's Ledger, 1949-1963 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Treasurer's Ledger, 1963-1985 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Sligo Supporters Club of New York Celebration Banquet, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, 2006, undated (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Publication: Sligo in New York: The Irish from Co. Sligo: 1849-1991. John T. Ridge. County Sligo Social and Benevolent Assocation. New York. 1991. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Events, 1984, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Sligo Banner, undated; cuid34978 (Box 54)
- XXVII. Tipperary, 1914-2004
  - Annual Ball, 1914, 1964, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Annual Ball, 1960, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Annual Ball, 1987-1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Annual Ball, 1992-1995 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Annial Ball, 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Annual Ball, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Annual Ball, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Annual Ball, 2003-2004 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Hurling, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Hurling Club Annual Dinner Dance, 1987, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Ladies Social and Benevolent Association Ball Programme (photocopy), Apr 4, 1914 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - N&B Association Annual Ball, 1965-1966, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - N&B Assocation Annual Ball, 2005, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Old I.R. A. Commemorative Calendar, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Photograph: N&B Association Annual Ball, Mar 4, 1959 (Box Shared Tamiment AIAXOS001, Folder 1)
  - The Tipperary Annual, 1947 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- XXVIII. Tyrone, 1983-2002
  - Pipe Band 50th Anniversary Dinner Dance, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Pipe Band Advertising Contract, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Society Annual Dinner Dance, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - The Story of the County Tyrone Society, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- XXIX. Waterford
- XXX. Westmeath
  - Photograph, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- XXXI. Wexford, 2004-2007
  - Annual Dinner Dance Anniversary Celebration, 2004, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Photograph, undated (Box 63, Folder 15)
- XXXII. Wicklow
  - Photographs, 2002, undated (Box 63, Folder 16)
- XXXIII. Unidentified, 1935
  - Photograph: St. Patrick's Day Dinner and Dance, Mar 16, 1935 (Box Shared Tamiment AIAXOS001, Folder 1)
  - Panoramic Photograph: 50th Annual Ball, United Irish Counties Association of New York, Inc., Hotel Commodore, Jan 15, 1954 (Box Shared Tamiment AIAXOS001, Folder 2)
- United Counties Banner, undated; cuid34977 (Box 53)